International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 99 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records 5535
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Telegrams, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 79)
- AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 1 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 2 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 3 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 4 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 5 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 6 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 7 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 8 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 9 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 10 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 11 of 11], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Birds Eye [folder 1 of 3], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Birds Eye [folder 2 of 3], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Birds Eye [folder 3 of 3], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Blue Cross - Blue Shield, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Bulletin Board Notices, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- C-B Foods, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Channel #13 [folder 1 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Channel #13 [folder 2 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Channel #13 [folder 3 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Channel #13 [folder 4 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 1 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 2 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 3 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 4 of 4], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Dental Insurance, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Eastern Conference, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Eye Glass Program, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Financial Report, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 6], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 6], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 6], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 6], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 6], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 6], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Minutes, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Monthly Meeting Notices, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Police Report on Stolen Goods from Office, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Political Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Retired members of Local 99, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- State of New York. Dept. of Labor, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Stewards [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Stewards [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 47)